if i would show anything with doctor this blog is so far
如果我愿意和医生做任何事情，这个博客到目前为止
series on the ban order
禁令系列
we now where the content add aiki 5 your basically
我们现在将内容添加到aiki 5的位置上
your site comment that facet and then you ta ke specify parameters
您的网站评论该方面，然后您指定参数
so that these are deeply appalled or parameters that such as you need home duos
这样您就深感震惊或需要诸如家用二重奏之类的参数
how to the great the day hello john de content and we go yes simple and will
如何度过美好的一天，你好，约翰·德·德内容
your day so that comes well can download content from must punch yogis away
您的一天很顺利，可以从必须打瑜伽的人那里下载内容
and the conditions the cm what when she tries to a that content backdrop that 5g on the
和条件厘米，当她尝试到5g的dat内容背景时，
cats debates man everytime such a show derby and we to be
猫每次都会在这样的表演德比中辩论，而我们将成为
able to reproduce idea cross media download this content that
能够通过跨媒体复制想法下载此内容
was popular at one point and the sunlight disk and then types topsy diet
一度流行，然后在阳光下晒盘，然后输入麻痹性饮食
and would be possible to realize that cd's
并有可能意识到cd的
she won the earth content to add the face and get this a cd that he downloaded
她赢得了大地的满足，为他添加了面孔并获得了一张他下载的CD
from this drug dyke structure the cost people know the origin if you who
从这种毒品堤坝的结构中，人们会知道成本，如果您
and they want to face using that catching iva we did feel the cold war liters
他们想面对使用这种俘获的iva，我们确实感觉到了冷战的升起
oil fuji after author joost kaesemans and that was one engines per file
作者joost kaesemans之后的石油富士，这是每个文件一个引擎
close then condition a myth detail so out there do those doors
关闭然后整理一个神话般的细节，所以在那里做那些门
automatically start the paramilitaries spicy joost I put seeds in one
准军事人员自动开始辛辣的工作，我把种子合二为一
luxury version vito that we will be next that time to just use your teaser for people to
豪华版vito，我们下次将使用您的预告片来吸引人们
you specify the day pointer espace is basically support from
您指定天指针espace基本上是从
with and the furtwangen is my own because oria the content and get and take specs
和furtwangen是我自己的，因为oria的内容以及获取和获取规格
and fiction that if you two have to do so at Idea Ryder
和虚构的故事，如果你们两个必须在Idea Ryder这么做
forget the soot looking for the root node in the us already that i put it with that
忘记了烟灰寻找我们在美国的根节点，我把它
and check out the one i would be happy with that did that before marmite has espace
并查看在marmite拥有espace之前我对此感到满意的那个
name we now what became a historian that photo and try box and cube
给我们起个名字，就是现在成为历史学家的照片，然后尝试将盒子和立方体
[Applause]
[掌声]